ANKITA NAIK

CONTACT

Address : 10A Breton Grove, Kingston, Wellington 6021

Phone: 0225475450

Email: ankinaik92@gmail.com

SKILLS

- HTML5, CSS3
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- JSON
- AngularJS
- Proficient in Adobe Suite
- InVision
- Agile Workflow
- Troubleshooting
- Teamwork
- Strong Verbal & Writing Communications
- Proficient in MS Office Suite
- Flexible & Adaptable

EDUCATION

Diploma in UI/UX, Mumbai, India 2018

Bachelor of Information Technology Mumbai, India, 2013

Visa Type: Partner of a Permanent Resident - Partnership Based Open Work Visa

Expiry Date: 24 July 2021

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Knowledgeable Web Designer with expert knowledge of HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, jQuery, JSON, and AngularJS, SEO and web analytics. Adept at planning, designing and implementing website structure and navigation layouts. Over 6 six years of experience working as a web designer for Marketing and Publishing business.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Retail Assistant, October 2020 till Present Look sharp Wellington

- Schedule freight pick-up and delivery appointments.
- Helping customers manage large purchases by collecting items from shelves and storage location.
- Increased sales by offering advice on purchases and promoting additional products.
- Checking prices for customers and processing items selling by scanning bar-codes, billing stocks using POS systems, and issuing payment receipt for customers.
- Fielded questions and solved problems by informing customers of promotions and store policies.
- Monitoring sales floor and merchandise displays for presentable condition, taking corrective action such as restocking or reorganizing products.
- Refunded payments for returned items, processed exchanges, and offered store credit to achieve customer satisfaction.
- Logged reports, expenses, receipts, and sales documents using MS Office suite.

Web Designer, September 2016 to December 2019 Equitymaster Agora Research Private Limited - Mumbai, India

- Provided front-end website development using Word Press.
- Met with clients to discuss expectations regarding visual presentation, branding, and e-commerce functionality.
- Designing User-Flow and User Journey Maps.
- Planned website development, converting mock-ups into usable web presence with HTML5, JavaScript, AJAX and JSON coding.
- Drafted customized layout, low-fidelity and high-fidelity wire-frames based on predetermined parameters, and expectations.
- Coded websites using HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, and jQuery languages.
- Converted graphic designs to usable web images using Adobe PhotoShop.
- Converted .psd to HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript.
- Generated custom coding to create web page content and functionality including shopping cart, two-step authentication, and mailing list management.
- Implemented coding based on commonly accepted standards to establish site layout and user interface.

- Writing Media queries to test the web page cross-browser, and device compatibility.
- Designing user-friendly responsive websites and mobile applications.
- Conducted testing and review of website design for responsiveness, clarity, and effectiveness.
- Conducted unit and functional testing over course of the web development lifecycle.
- Implementing changes and integrating requested elements to streamline business operations.
- Employed search engine optimization tactics to increase the reach of the targeted audience.
- Implemented website maintenance, content management, update, and security resource tutorials to assist end-user training.
- Completed full redesigns of existing websites to improve navigation, enhance visuals and strengthen search engine rankings.
- Authoring user feedback reports for use in future updates.
- Applied both qualitative and quantitative analysis techniques to continuously improve end-user experiences.

eBook Developer, April 2014 to September 2016 Cenveo Publisher Services - Mumbai, India

- Interaction with clients for detailed requirements for eBook content.
- Converted design files (InDesign, PDF, MS Word) into eBooks.
- Creating Mathematical equations on iMathEQ for eBooks and testing on cross devices.
- Created reflowable and fixed-layout ePub 2/3, Kindle Format, iPad, and Tablet.
- Responsible for end-to-end testing over eBook development lifecycle.
- Implementing the feedback from clients with immediate effect.

Community Work & Experience

Computer Trainer - Digital Inclusion Alliance Aotearoa December 2019 - October 2020

- Provided instruction on professional technology use and web etiquette.
- Assisting students where requiring extra help.
- Planned detailed lesson plans with related handouts to teach stepby-step computer use to students like MS Office, Online Shopping and Bankings, Gmail, Frauds, Scams.
- Monitored student progress through frequent assessments of various computer tasks.
- Instructed students according to skill level and of different age groups.